A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE) files FA740
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Awardees – Multi-Institutional (not Fund Administered), 1944-1966; III; 115.2 Cubic Feet 96 boxes.
  - Armed Forces Project, 1944-1956; 2; 9.6 Cubic Feet 8 boxes.; 8 boxes.
    - Training Materials and Reports
      - Citizenship Hours - Contacts, n.d. (Box 3 (49645))
      - Communism - Merle Fainsod material, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - American Communisim, Tactics and Activities in the U.S. - Brown (Box 3 (49645))
      - Hours on Communism, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Communism in France and Italy (Box 3 (49645))
      - Communism - George F. Kennan lecture at Miss. Fines' School regarding "The Russians", 1951 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Comments on Communism materials - Rostow, Fainsod and Almond (Box 3 (49645))
      - Communism - Rostow material, n.d. (Box 3 (49645))
      - Communism - Gabriel Almond material, 1951-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Orientation to Foreign Cultures - Suggested consultants, n.d. (Box 3 (49645))
      - Understanding Other Cultures and their People (Box 3 (49645))
      - International Problems Consultants - George Spindler, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - West Point Consultants - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Annapolis Consultants, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Plischke, Elmer - University of Maryland, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Strengthening American Education - Address by Earl James McGrath, 1951 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Wiley, Marshall W. - Democratic Symbolism, 1951 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Litterick, William - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Litterick, William - Special File, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Bartky, John, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Civilian and Service Comments, 1952-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Loyalty; You and Your Representative Government - Drafts with General's coments, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Office Equipment, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Office Space, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Advisory Board, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Other Projects, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Anti-Segregation [Refers to Ashmore Project], 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Teaching material drafts with Fund office comments, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Your Chain of Command - Pamphlet and guide (Box 3 (49645))
      - The Constitution - Pamphlet and guide (Box 3 (49645))
      - Your Economic Freedom - Pamphlet and guide (Box 3 (49645))
      - Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Your Fighting Team - Pamphlet and guide, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Loyalty - Pamphlet and guide, 1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Tallies of evaluation tests, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Policy Directives - Armed Forces Discussion Hours, 1953 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Reports, 1952-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Reports - Bowles Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Kunhardt, Keith R., 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Eurich, Alvin C., 1953-1954 (Box 3 (49645))
      - Log of activities, 1953-1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Bi-weekly reports, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Information School - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Information School - Course materials [2 Folders], 1951-1952 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Information School - Course materials - International relations, 1951-1952 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Fort Belvoir - Command conference, 1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Fort Ord, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Indiantown Gap; Carlisle, PA; and Second Army, 1952-1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Ford Leonard Wood, 1952-1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Project The Bill of Rights [Drafts], 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Project - Chain of Command, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Constitution - Pamphlet draft, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Citizenship Hour - Declaration of Independence (Box 4 (49646))
      - Freedom of Enterprise, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - Loyalty - Drafts of guide, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Propaganda (Box 4 (49646))
      - Freedom and Responsibility (Box 4 (49646))
      - Integrity, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - Honesty and Integrity [not created by Ford Foundation] (Box 4 (49646))
      - Your Fighting Team - Pamphlet drafts, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Your New Citizenship - Pamphlet drafts, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - You and Your Economic Freedom - Guide drafts, 1953-1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Your and Your Military Service - Pamphlet drafts, 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Citizenship Hours - Group Leader's Manual, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - Citizenship Hours - Drafts, n.d. (Box 4 (49646))
      - Army Education Program for Inactive Theaters - Manual, 1944 (Box 4 (49646))
      - U.S. Government Printing Office Publications, 1946-1952 (Box 4 (49646))
      - History of the Army Education Program, 1945 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Information School Materials, [1947-1952] (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Information School - Miscellaneous printed material, 1947-1955 (Box 4 (49646))
      - A Guide for the Study of Modern Basic Strategy and Tactics, [1948] (Box 4 (49646))
      - Armed Forces Talks, 1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Clippings, 1951 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Generals of the Army - Booklet, 1953 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Your and Your USA - Publications [Includes oversized posters, folded], 1954 (Box 4 (49646))
        - [Posters], 2015:007:001
      - Your and Your USA - Publications [Includes oversized posters, folded], 1955 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Know Your Communist Enemy - Publications [Includes oversized posters, folded], 1955 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Attitudes Toward Military Service as a Career - Survey [2 copies], 1955 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Your Life Plans and the Armed Forces - American Council on Education, 1955 (Box 4 (49646))
      - Activity Report of Washington Group and Sample of Materials Developed and in Process of Field Testing - Report by W. Litterick (Box 5 (49647))
      - Administrative history and preliminary explorations and plans, 1951-1954 (Box 5 (49647))
      - The Theory and Practice of International Communism - Report by W. Rostow (Box 5 (49647))
      - Armed Forces Information and Education Division - Publications, 1950-1951 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Joe Sconce Letters, 1951 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Research Division Reports, 1951-1956 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Strengthening the Free World Economy, 1952 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Armed Forces Education Program - Committee meeting, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Citizen Education in World Affairs - Report by Bernard C. Cohen, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - United States Foreign Economic Policy and the Sterling Area - Memorandum by James Nelson and Donald Palmer, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Communism in the United States - Outline, [1954] (Box 5 (49647))
      - Background and Origins of Communism with Emphasis on the Internal Situation in Russia - by Merle Fainsod, [1954] (Box 5 (49647))
      - International Communism Series - Moscow and Chinese Communism 1923-1953 - W. Rostow, [1954] (Box 5 (49647))
      - Series - Your America, No.1-10 [Navy Department Publication], 1949 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Armed Forces Talk - Publication [3 Folders], 1948-1951 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Miscellaneous publications, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (49647))
      - War Department Readjustment Regulations, 1944-1946 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Army Information Digest - Publications, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy - Miscellaneous publications, 1950-1952 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy Citizenship Program, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy - Miscellaneous correspondence and material on education programs, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy - Bainbridge, MD, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy - Great Lakes, [1952-1954] (Box 5 (49647))
      - Navy - San Diego, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (49647))
      - U.S. Marine Corps - Sanford Kahrmann, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - U.S. Marine Corps - San Diego, 1953 (Box 5 (49647))
      - U.S. Marine Corps - Camp Pendleton, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Courtesy Reports to Armed Forces Branches, 1954 (Box 5 (49647))
      - Catalogue of information and education materials, 1950-1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Kinescopes and films, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Armed Forces Citizenship Hours [Film treatment], 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Evaluation of newsmaps and broadcasts, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - United States Armed Forces Institute, 1952-1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Armed Forces Press and Radio Service, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Armed Forces Project, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Personnel [Project Applicants], 1952-1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Frank C. Bowles, 1952-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Harrison, John F - Correspondence [Photograph], 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Kahrmann, Sanford - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Fiser, Webb S., 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Jennings, Frank, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Booker, Floyde E., 1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Consultants - General, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Colonial Williamsburg - Decision at Williamsburg, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Burton Wright - Defining Committee's work, 1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Maxwell Graduate School of Citizenship and Public Affairs [Syracuse], 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Communism Consultants - General [Includes signature of George Kennan], 1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Rostow, William W. [Includes signatures], 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Almond, Gabriel, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Fainsod, Merle, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Walsh, Warren, 1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Russia - Pamphlet and Group Leader's guide - by C. P. Lemieux, 1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Memorandum on editorial situation, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Origins and Penetration Tactics of International Communism - Watnik, 1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Imprisonment of the Mind: Effect of Indoctrination in Jail upon Two Young Americans who had just been Released by the Chinese Communists - Barnett, Doak, 1955 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Information and Education Press, Fort Slocum, New York, 1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Handbooks - Oral Communications; and Policy and Operational Procedures, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Grady Education Case Study, 1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Education Program - Special Text, 1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Armed Forces Extension Course - Common subcourse, n.d. (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of Defense Directives, 1949-1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of the Army - Troop information, 1944-1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Troop Information - Draft, [1952] (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of Air Force Information, 1950-1951 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of the Navy, 1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - U.S. Navy Education - Evaluation, [1952] (Box 6 (49648))
      - Marine Corps, 1950-1952 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of Defense Directives - Includes information about the Military Personnel Policy Committee, 1949-1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Office of Director of Armed Forces Information and Education, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Report of TDY Mission to French Morocco and European Community, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Reorganization of Research Division, 1953 (Box 6 (49648))
      - Department of Army - Training Publications - Troop Topics, 1951-1952 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Department of Army - Officer Training Publications, 1952 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Department of Army - Officer Education Publications, 1952 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) related publications, 1953-1954 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Study of Information and Education Activities World War II - by Francis Keppel, 1946 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Armed Forces Project - History [Includes statement by Brig. General Lanham; Survey fo Troop Information Program; and A Report to the President by President's Committee on Religion and Welfare in the Armed Forces, 1949 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Matthews, Herbert L. - Greetings from the President - Manuscript, [1951] (Box 7 (49649))
      - Department of Defense - Official statements and memoranda, 1952-1953 (Box 7 (49649))
      - International Problems - Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Office of the Chief of Army Field Forces, 1953 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Comments on Instructor's Manual, 1953 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Terminal Report - Draft, n.d. (Box 7 (49649))
      - Washington staff correspondence - Sanford Kahrmann, 1953 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Camp Roberts Material - Quiz results, 1953 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Citizenship Development - Freedom vs. Responsibility, n.d. (Box 7 (49649))
      - How Communism Came to Russia - Drafts by Walsh, 1954 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Communism in China - Draft by Watnick, 1954 (Box 7 (49649))
      - Armed Forces - Publications and posters [2 Folders; oversized posters folded], 1954 (Box 7 (49649))
        - [posters], 2015:007:002
        - [posters], 2015:007:003
      - Citizenship Series - Instruction Guide and Pamphlet [2 Folders] (Box 7 (49649))
      - World Problems Series - Instruction Guide and Pamphlet [2 Folders], undated (Box 8 (49650))
      - Know Your Communist Enemy Series - Instruction Guide and Pamphlet [2 Folders] (Box 8 (49650))
  - California and Western Conference Cost and Statistical Study, 1953-1958; 3; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 box.; 1 box.
    The California and Western Conference Statistical Study sub-series consists of reports and memoranda regarding a joint study by eleven universities about factors affecting the cost of American higher education during a time of growing enrollment and demands for wider educational services.
    - California and Western Conference Cost and Statistical Study [Bound volume], 1956 (Box 1 (49651))
    - California and Western Conference - Study - Cost and Statistics - Attachments, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49651))
    - California and Western Conference - Study - Cost and Statistics - Grant, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (49651))
    - California and Western Conference - Study - Cost and Statistics - Grant - Supplementary, 1956-1958 (Box 1 (49651))
    - Big Ten Survey, 1955 (Box 1 (49651))
    - Survey Instructions, 1955 (Box 1 (49651))
  - College Self-Studies Program, 1945-1960; 4; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 boxes.; The College Self-Studies Program sub-series contains general data, grant information and reports from the individual colleges and universities that participated in the program.
    4 boxes.
    - Self Studies - General correspondence, A-B, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - General correspondence, D-F, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - General correspondence, J-L, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - General correspondence, M-N, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - General data, 1952-1956 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - General data, 1951-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Evaluation sheets, A-L (approved and rejected), 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Evaluation sheets, M-Z (approved and rejected), 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Evaluation sheets (all), 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Charts - Summaries (#1), 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Charts - Summaries (#2), 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Allegheny College - Audit Report, June 30, 1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Allegheny College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Beloit College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1958 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Brooklyn College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Brown University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Buffalo University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Carleton College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - City College of New York - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Colby College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Cornell College (Iowa) - General - Grants and supporting data [PHOTOGRAPHS], 1952-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - DePauw University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Dillard University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Drake University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Earlham College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Florida, University of - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Goucher College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Hampton Institute - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Heidelberg College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Hope College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Iowa, State University of - General - Grants and supporting data, 1945-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Jamestown College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Lafayette College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Lincoln University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - North Carolina, University of - First State of the University Conference, 3/3-4/1953 - Proceedings (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - North Carolina, University of - Second State of the University Conference, 2/18-19/1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - North Carolina, University of - General - Grants and supporting data, 1954-1960 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Notre Dame University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Ohio Wesleyan University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Parsons School of Design - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Pittsburgh, University of - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Reed College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Rutgers University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1958 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - St. Francis Xavier for Women - General - Grants and supporting data, 1945-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - St. John's College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - St. Olaf College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Scripps College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Southern Methodist University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Southwestern at Memphis - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Stanford University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Wellesley College - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Wesleyan University - General - Grants and supporting data, 1952-1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Committee on College Self Studies - Members Report (Father Hesburgh, Margaret Clapp, Byron Trippett), 1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Conference - Highland Park, 6/18-20/1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Conference - Princeton, 12/3-4/1954, and reports (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Donaldson - Fortifying Higher Education: A Story of College Self Studies, 1959 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Final Report, 1953-1957 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Report notes - Extras (#1), 1954 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Report draft - Extras (#2), 1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Results, 1955 (Box 1 (49652))
    - Self Studies - Allegheny College - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Beloit College - Reports (1/3), 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Beloit College - Reports (2/3), 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Beloit College - Reports (3/3), 1953-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Bowdoin College - Reports, 1954 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Brooklyn College - Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Brown University - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Buffalo University - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Carleton College - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Carleton College - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - City College of New York - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Colby College - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Cornell College (Iowa) - Reports, 1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Cornell College (Iowa) - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - DePauw University - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Dillard University - Reports, 1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Dillard University - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Drake University - Reports, 1952-1957 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Earlham College - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Florida, University of - Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Goucher College - Reports, 1953 (Box 2 (49653))
    - Self Studies - Hampton Institute - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Heidelberg College - Reports, 1954 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Hope College - Reports, 1954 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Iowa, State University of - Reports, 1954-1956 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Jamestown College - Reports, 1954 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Lafayette College - Reports (plus bound report not in folder), 1953-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Lincoln University - Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Michigan Institute of Higher Education - Reports, 1958 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - New York University - Reports, 1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - North Carolina State College - Reports, 1953 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - North Carolina, University of - Reports, 1953 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Notre Dame, University of - Reports, 1954 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Ohio Wesleyan University - Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Parson School of Design - Reports, 1954-1956 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Pittsburgh, University of - Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Reed College - Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - Rutgers University - Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 3 (49654))
    - Self Studies - St. John's College - Reports, 1952-1955 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - St. Olaf College - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - St. Xavier College - Reports, 1953 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - St. Xavier College - Reports, 1953-1958 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - St. Xavier College - Reports, 1954 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - St. Xavier College - Reports, 1955-1959 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - Scripps College - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 4 (49655))
    - Self Studies - Southern Methodist University - Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 4 (49655))